For two days now, the world has been waiting for Donald Trump to decide whether to accept
两天来，全世界都在等唐纳德·特朗普决定是否接受
Israel's evite to go to war with Iran.
以色列发来的"对伊朗开战"邀请。
We know he's viewed it, but he still has an RSVP.
我们知道他已经看了，但还没回复"是否出席"。
I hate it when that happens.
我最讨厌这种情况了。
Now, in the meantime, the question has started a separate war inside his MAGA base.
与此同时，这个问题已经在他的MAGA基本盘内部引发了另一场战争。
And today, it exploded into a heated debate between the two most likable and charming voices
今天，它爆发成了一场激烈辩论，交战双方是右翼阵营中
on the right.
最"可爱"、最"有魅力"的两个声音。
On the one side is Ted Cruz, who wants war with Iran.
一边是想对伊朗开战的泰德·克鲁兹。
And on the other is Tucker Carlson, who thinks Ted Cruz doesn't know shit about Israel.
另一边是塔克·卡尔森，他觉得泰德·克鲁兹对伊朗屁都不懂。
How many people live in Iran, by the way?
顺便问一下，伊朗有多少人口？
I don't know the population at all.
我完全不知道人口数字。
No, I don't know the population.
不，我不知道人口。
You don't know the population in the country you seek to topple?
你想推翻的那个国家有多少人口你都不知道？
How many people live in Iran?
伊朗有多少人？
92 million.
九千二百万。
Oh, damn, Ted Cruz.
哦，该死，泰德·克鲁兹。
Are you a pair of $800 Farragamo boat shoes?
你是一双800美元的菲拉格慕船鞋吗？
Tucker Carlson owned you, buddy.
塔克·卡尔森把你完爆了，老兄。
Ted Cruz was like, I know the population.
泰德·克鲁兹的反应是："我知道人口数字。"
Just give me a second to count, okay?
"给我一秒钟数一下，好吗？"
Let's see, there's the Ayatollah.
"让我看看，有阿亚图拉。"
That's one.
"那是一个。"
The Iron Cheek, too, is a Latin one.
"还有铁面颊，他也算拉丁裔。"
I don't know.
"我不知道。"
No.
"不。"
If you enjoyed seeing Ted Cruz get metaphorically punched in the face, how'd you like to see it again?
如果你喜欢看泰德·克鲁兹被狠狠打脸，想再看一遍吗？
Why is it relevant, whether it will be because 90 million or 80 million or 100 million?
为什么这很重要，不管是九千万还是八千万还是一亿？
Why is that relevant?
为什么这很重要？
Because if you don't know anything about the country, I didn't say I don't know anything
因为如果你对这个国家一无所知，我没说我一无所知
about it.
关于它。
Okay, what's the ethnic mix abroad?
好吧，那边的种族构成是什么？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Not ethnic mixes.
不是种族构成问题。
You don't want to go toe to toe with Tucker Carlson on ethnic mixes.
你可不想在种族构成问题上跟塔克·卡尔森硬碰硬。
That's his best subject.
那是他的拿手好戏。
Look at poor Ted Cruz.
看看可怜的泰德·克鲁兹。
He's like, I'd like to photo-friend, please.
他就像在说："我想找个朋友求助，拜托了。"
Oh, shit, I don't have any.
"哦，该死，我没有朋友。"
I had a waiter last night at Outback and he called me champ.
"昨晚在澳拜客有个服务员叫我'冠军'。"
Can I phone him?
"我可以打电话给他吗？"
You know, I can't believe I'm saying this, but I'm starting to feel bad for Ted Cruz.
你知道，我不敢相信我会这么说，但我开始为泰德·克鲁兹感到难过了。
So come on, Ted, you got this.
加油泰德，你可以的!
They are Persians and predominantly Shia.
他们是波斯人，主要是什叶派。
Okay.
好的。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
It's not even, you don't know anything about Iran.
你对伊朗根本一无所知。
Okay, I am not the Tucker Carlson expert on Iran, who says he's calling to go over
好吧，我不是塔克·卡尔森那样的伊朗专家，他说他打电话来
the government and he's calling to go over the country.
推翻政府，他打电话来推翻这个国家。
No, you don't know anything about the country.
不，你对这个国家一无所知。
This is awsome.
这真是太棒了。
You don't know anything.
你什么都不知道。
No, you don't know anything.
不，你什么都不知道。
I don't care about who wins the fight.
我不在乎谁赢得这场打斗。
I just like watching the fight.
我就是喜欢看打架。
It's like alien versus predator, but somehow more gross.
这就像异形大战铁血战士，但不知怎么的更恶心。
You can see how heated this is getting.
你可以看到这事儿吵得有多激烈了。
Clearly, Maga is much more divided about whether to overthrow Iran than they were about
很明显，在"是否要推翻伊朗"这个问题上，MAGA阵营的分歧
whether to overthrow America.
比他们当初在"是否要推翻美国"时还大。
I think a little comment in this interview turned into a semantic battle.
我觉得这次采访里的每句话都演变成了文字游戏。
Really believe that.
我真的相信。
We are carrying out military strikes today.
我们今天正在执行军事打击。
You said Israel was.
你刚才说"是以色列"。
Right, with our help.
对，有我们帮忙。
I'm said we, Israel is leading them, but we're supporting them.
我说的是"我们"，是以色列在主导，但我们在支援。
Well, this, you're breaking news here because the US government last night denied the
哦，你这可是爆了个大料啊，因为美国政府昨晚刚否认了，
National Security Council spokesman Alex Pfeiffer denied on behalf of Trump that we were
国家安全委员会发言人亚历克斯·菲佛代表特朗普否认了我们
acting on Israel's behalf in any offensive capacity.
代表以色列采取了任何进攻性行动。
Now, we're not bombing them.
现在，我们没有在轰炸他们。
Israel's bombing them.
是以色列在轰炸他们。
You just said we were.
你刚才明明说"我们"了。
We are supporting Israel as well.
我们也在支援以色列。
We?
我们？
I?
我？
You?
你？
For the party that promised no confusion around pronouns, this is really confusing.
对于一个承诺在"代词"问题上绝不搞混的政党来说，这可真是够混乱的了。
The point is, Maga World is tearing itself apart and everyone is waiting for Trump to
重点是，MAGA世界正在疯狂内斗，所有人都在等着特朗普
make a decision.
做决定。
And remember, Trump abruptly left the G7 summit so he could rush back to the White House, meet
记住，特朗普突然退出了G7峰会，就为了火速赶回白宫，
with his National Security team in the situation room and decide if he's bringing America into
和他的国安团队在战情室开会，然后决定是否要
this war.
把美国拖入这场战争。
So, we were all waiting for the big announcement.
所以，我们都在等那个重磅官宣。
And then it came.
然后，它来了。
Trump said in a truth social post, it is my great honor to announce that I will be putting
特朗普在"真相社交"上发帖说："我非常荣幸地宣布，我将会
up two beautiful flag polls on both sides of the White House and North and South Lawns.
在白宫的两侧，也就是南草坪和北草坪上，竖起两根漂亮的旗杆。"
Yes, that is definitely an announcement.
是的，这绝对算是个"官宣"。
Not the announcement we were waiting for, but sure, have a couple flag polls installed
虽然不是我们等的那个，但行吧，在白宫装几根旗杆就装吧。
at the White House.
在白宫。
That will be something for the groundskeepers to take care of while you're busy in the
这样当您在战情室里忙着处理更重要的大事时，
situation room dealing with more important matters.
园丁们也总算有活儿干了。
At 11 o'clock we're lifting the flag, but we're going to lift the poll now and then they
"11点钟我们会升旗，但我们现在先把杆子立起来，然后他们
go into the other side.
再去另一边。"
Okay.
"好的。"
But I'd be out there introducing the whole thing.
"但我会亲自到场介绍整个过程。"
Now, back to the situation room.
"现在，回到战情室。"
So we'll have one on this side of the building.
"所以大楼这边会有一根。"
We'll have one on that side of the building properly placed.
"那一边也有一根，位置都摆得很好。"
These are the best polls anywhere in the country, in the world, actually.
"这些是全美国，不，实际上是全世界最棒的旗杆。"
They're tapered.
"它们是锥形的。"
They have the nice top.
"顶部也很漂亮。"
I don't know if you people are aesthetic.
"我不知道你们这些人有没有审美。"
You know they're the fake news.
"你们知道他们是假新闻。"
I don't know about it.
"那个我不好说。"
I don't know there.
"我不了解他们。"
But it's a very exciting project to meet.
"但对我来说，这是个非常激动人心的项目。"
What's going on here?
这到底是什么情况？
Feels like someone told him, sir, you're not doing well in the polls and he was like,
感觉就像有人跟他说："先生，您在'民调'里的数据不太好看。"
I hear you, I'm on it.
然后他回答："我听到了，我这就处理。"
And by the way, what was that aside about how the fake news doesn't understand flag poll
话说回来，他那句关于"假新闻"不懂旗杆
aesthetics?
美学的话是什么意思？
I mean, this is a whole new stereotype of the liberal media I didn't even know about.
我的天，这简直是给自由派媒体创造了一个全新的刻板印象。
They live on 100 Binds laptop and they have no appreciation for tapered flag polls.
"他们整天纠结于亨特·拜登的笔记本电脑，而且对锥形旗杆完全不懂欣赏。"
Now, personally, I think it's cool that Trump found a new use for the 50-foot poll that
不过，个人觉得特朗普总算给那根50英尺长、
Melania refuses to touch him with.
梅拉尼娅拒绝碰的长杆找到了新用处，还挺酷的。
He was clearly having a good time, although he stopped himself from getting too carried
他显然玩得很开心，尽管他还是克制住了自己，没让自己太
away.
得意忘形。
Let's have a good, they call it a lifting.
"让我们来一次体面的，他们叫它'升举'。"
They also use another word, but I'm not going to use that word.
"他们也用另一个词，不过我可不用那个词。"
You know that is?
"你知道是哪个词吧？"
The word starts with an E. You know what the word is?
"那个词是以E开头的。你们知道是什么词吧？"
If I haven't used it, I'd be run out of town by you people.
"我要是用了，你们这帮人早就把我轰出去了。"
All right, so enjoy it.
"好吧，那就好好享受吧。"
Come on, Donald.
拜托，唐纳德。
You think if you say the word erection, we're going to all act like children and take it
你以为如果你说"勃起"这个词，我们就会像小孩子一样
out of context.
断章取义吗？
I mean, come on.
我是说，拜托。
Come on.
拜托。
Where'd you get a silly idea like that?
你从哪儿得出这种愚蠢的想法的？
I'm going to come.
我要来了。
Okay, y'all.
好的，各位。
Now I remember, right.
现在我想起来了，对吧。
It's crazy for Trump to suddenly get all worried about saying erection.
特朗普突然对说"勃起"这个词变得小心翼翼，真是太疯狂了。
His closing campaign message was vote for me.
他的竞选结束语是"投票给我。"
I saw Arnold Palmer's incredible penis.
"我见过阿诺德·帕尔默那令人难以置信的阴茎。"
But okay, you came out, you talked about flag polls, you've met the flagpole guys, you
但好吧，你出来了，你谈论了旗杆，你见了旗杆工人，你
made some flagpole-related dick jokes, time to turn around, go back inside and stop and
开了一些跟旗杆有关的老二笑话，是时候转身回屋里
or escalate this war.
停止或升级这场战争了。
Let's not waste any more time.
咱们别再浪费时间了。
Say what you want about Biden.
你们可以随便说拜登什么。
He was it for open borders.
他支持开放边境。
He wasn't for transgender for everybody.
他不支持人人都变性。
We don't know where it's coming from, sir.
"我们不知道这是从哪儿来的，先生。"
I said, check out the tariffs.
"我说，看看关税。"
He calls back about a day later.
"他一天后打电话回来。"
Wow.
"哇。"
Somewhere in this group, somebody that is going to captivate some movie producer, not
"在这群人里的某个地方，有人会吸引某个电影制片人，不是
every Wednesday.
每个星期三。"
The only thing too late is Powell.
"唯一太晚的是鲍威尔。"
Powell's too late.
"鲍威尔太晚了。"
Too late, pal.
"太晚了，伙计。"
Let's have dinner.
"我们吃晚饭吧。"
Too late.
"太晚了。"
You ever have a guy that's not a smart person and you're dealing with it.
"你有没有遇到过一个不聪明的人，然后你在应付他。"
Any legal immigrant?
"任何合法移民？"
Thirty-five club championships.
"35个俱乐部冠军。"
You all know that.
"你们都知道这个。"
Groceries are down, eggs are down, you know the eggs.
"日用品价格下降了，鸡蛋价格下降了，你知道，鸡蛋。"
You know what I do whenever they talk about Gavin Newskin?
"你知道每当他们谈论加文·纽森时我会怎么做吗？"
I say, look at the real.
"我说，看看真实的。"
Austria has very, very flammable cheese.
"奥地利有非常非常易燃的奶酪。"
Good Lord.
我的天啊。
I don't want to say anything, but if your flagpole erections last more than four hours,
我不想说什么，但如果你的旗杆"勃起"持续超过四小时，
you probably want to see a doctor.
你可能需要看医生了。
Donald.
唐纳德。
Focus.
专注。
Focus, focus, focus.
专注，专注，专注。
Get back to the flag, Paul.
回到旗杆，保罗。
No way.
不对。
Get back to the war.
回到战争。
I mean, war.
我是说，战争。
He's got me all mixed up.
他把我都搞混了。
Just someone, ask him about the war.
谁来问问他关于战争的事。
Have you even answered questions about whether you are moving closer or you believe the US
你有没有回答过关于你是否正在接近或者你是否相信美国
is moving closer to striking Iranian nuclear facilities?
正在接近打击伊朗核设施的问题？
Where's your mindset on that?
你对此的想法是什么？
I may do it.
我可能会做。
I may not do it.
我可能不会做。
I mean, nobody knows what I'm going to do.
我是说，没有人知道我要做什么。
Right.
对。
Super-helpful.
超级有用。
Thanks, guy.
谢谢，老兄。
That is the key to this whole thing.
这就是整件事的关键。
Nobody knows what he wants to do, including Donald Trump.
没有人知道他想做什么，包括唐纳德·特朗普自己。
You'd rather be doing home renovation projects than figure out how to fix all his
他宁愿做家庭装修项目，也不想弄清楚如何收拾他所有的
f**ks.
烂摊子。
And honestly, I agree.
说实话，我赞成。
I think we should encourage him to spend all his time on landscaping projects as opposed
我觉得我们应该鼓励他把所有时间都花在园林绿化项目上，而不是
to bringing America into another Middle East war.
把美国拖入另一场中东战争。
Frankly, a lot of people would be relieved by that decision, even overjoyed.
坦率地说，很多人会因为这个决定而松一口气，甚至欣喜若狂。
It might even give people...
这甚至可能给人们...
I don't want to say it, but it starts with an egg.
我不想说出来，但它以"蛋"开头。